Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series II (Box 49)
  - Sidney Hillman Foundation
    - "The Court Sits ...," Goldberg, Arthur J., undated. (Folder 117: 19)
    - "Freedom Is more than Academic," Keppel, Francis, undated. (Folder 117: 20)
    - "China Policy for the 70's," Kennedy, Edward M., undated. (Folder 117: 21)
    - "Where do we go from Here: Chaos or Community," King, Martin Luther, Jr., undated. (Folder 117: 22)
    - "The Working-Class Majority," Levison, Andrew, undated. (Folder 117: 23)
    - "Labor's Wrongs and Rights," Smith, William J., undated. (Folder 117: 24)
    - "Democracy and Peace," Thant, U., undated. (Folder 117: 25)
    - "The American City: Mirror to Man," Ylvisaker, Paul, undated. (Folder 117: 26)
    - "Conservation and the Future," Udall, Stewart L., undated. (Folder 117: 27)
  - Simon and Schuster--"The Jack Acid Society: Pogo as told to Walt Kelly,", 1957. (Folder 117: 28)
  - Sinclair, Upton
    - "I, Governor of California ...,", undated. (Folder 117: 29)
    - "Immediate Epic ...,", undated. (Folder 117: 30)
    - "Your Million Dollars,", 1939. (Folder 117: 31)
  - Sligh Realty Company--"The Story of the Rights of Man ...,", undated. (Folder 117: 32)
  - Slocomb, Whitney H., "Do you Want ...,", 1953. (Folder 117: 33)
  - Smoloskyp
    - Karavansky, Svyatoslav, undated. (Folder 117: 34)
    - "Trials in Ukraine 1972,", undated. (Folder 117: 35)
    - Moroz, Valentyn, 1970. (Folder 117: 36)
  - Strokata, Nina, 1972. (Folder 117: 37)
  - Snow, John Howland, "The Case of Tyler Kent,", 1965. (Folder 117: 38)
  - Social Democratic Federation--Morris, William, 1885-1891. (Folder 117: 39)
  - Social Democratic Publishing Company--"The Constructive ...," Thompson, 1908. (Folder 117: 40)
  - Social Science Publishers--Nearing, Scott
    - "Glimpses of the Soviet Republic,", 1926. (Folder 117: 41)
    - "Russia Turns East,", 1926. (Folder 117: 42)
  - "Socialism Unmasked,", 1912. (Folder 117: 43)
  - Socialist Call--"Debate Which Road for ...,", 1936. (Folder 117: 44)
  - Socialistic Co-Operative Publishing Association--"The Religion of Capital ...," Lafargue, Paul, and "Social Effect of Machinery," Cotton, Frank W., 1902. (Folder 117: 45)
  - Socialist Labor Party--Pamphlets
    - "The Class Struggle," Kautsky, Karl, 1900 (Folder 117: 46)
    - "The Chicago Martyrs Vindicated ...," Forker, Max, 1894 (Folder 117: 47)
  - Socialist Party USA--"National Platform ...,", undated. (Box-folder 118: 1)
  - Socialist League
    - "Workers' Control," Clay, Harold, undated. (Folder 118: 2)
    - "The Paris Commune,", 1871. (Folder 118: 3)
    - "Chants for Socialists," Morris, William, 1885. (Folder 118: 4)
      Collection of poems
  - Socialist Party--"Make an End of War," Mills, Walter Thomas, and "Big Business and War," Russell, Charles Edward, 1915. (Folder 118: 5)
  - Socialist Party--Social Democratic Federation
    - "Socialist Platform 1960,", undated. (Folder 118: 6)
    - "A Way Forward ...,", undated. (Folder 118: 7)
  - Socialist Party of America--"The Specialist Primer," Young, Art, 1930. (Folder 118: 8)
  - Socialist Party U.S.A.--"Socialist Handbook,", 1937. (Folder 118: 9)
  - Socialist Party of the United States--"Canton Speech," Debs, Eugene V., 1918. (Folder 118: 10)
  - Socialist Party U.S.A.--"Is the New Deal Socialism ...?" Thomas, Norman, 1936. (Folder 118: 11)
  - Socialist Workers Campaign--"Women's Liberation ...,", undated. (Folder 118: 12)
  - Socialist Workers Party
    - "1952 Election Platform ...,", circa 1952. (Folder 118: 13)
    - "Manifesto of the Fourth International on ...,", 1940. (Folder 118: 14)
    - "Vote for Socialism in 1956,", undated. (Folder 118: 15)
  - Socialist Workers Party and Young Peoples Socialist League--"How to Fight War ...?" Burnham, James, 1938. (Folder 118: 16)
  - Society for the Prevention of World War III, Inc.
    - "Deutschtum and America," Brown, John, undated. (Folder 118: 17)
    - "Comments and Documents ...," Foerster, F. W., 1944. (Folder 118: 18)
    - "Pan-Germanism ...," Tetens, T. H., undated. (Folder 118: 19)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science
    - "Man and the Atom," Born, Max, undated. (Folder 118: 20)
  - Society for Social Responsibility in Science
    - "Three Essays in ...," Lonsdale, Kathleen, Victor Paschkis, and O. T. Benfey, undated. (Folder 118: 21)
    - "Science and Conscience," Steenbeck, Max, 1964. (Folder 118: 22)
    - "Social Responsibility ...," Morgan, Arthur E., undated. (Folder 118: 23)
  - Sodality Union--"Wolves in Sheep's Clothing ...,", 1937. (Folder 118: 24)
  - Sofia Press
    - "How the Bulgarian ...," Anguelov, Dimiter, 1976. (Folder 118: 25)
    - "Along the Road of ...," Zhivkov, Todor, 1978. (Folder 118: 26)
  - Sons of Liberty--"The Socialist Network," Webster, Nesta H., 1926. (Folder 118: 27)
  - South African Department of Information--"A 'Ghetto' in South Africa,", undated. (Folder 118: 28)
  - South African Embassy--"All the Facts ...,", 1978. (Folder 118: 29)
  - South Avenue Methodist Church--"Giddy Minds ...," Manne, Roy E., 1951. (Folder 118: 30)
  - South-East Asia Treaty Organization--"Security in Rural Areas," Hyde, Douglas, 1968. (Folder 118: 31)
    Seminar
  - South Viet Nam--President Nguyen Van Thieu, 1969. (Folder 118: 32)
  - Southern California Committee against Neo-Nazism and Anti-Semitism--"The Silence ...,", 1949?. (Folder 118: 33)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare--"For Your Children Too,", undated. (Folder 118: 34)
  - Southern Regional Council
    - "Comprehensive Health Care ...," Anderson, Robert E., and Susan Morgan, 1973. (Folder 118: 35)
    - "The Migrant Farmer," Coles, Robert, 1965. (Folder 118: 36)
    - "John Willie Reed ...," Weltner, Charles Longstreet, 1969. (Folder 118: 37)
  - Southern States Industrial Council
    - "What Is Free Enterprise?" Horrigan, Anthony, undated. (Folder 118: 38)
    - "Opposing the Civil Rights Bill ...," Taylor, Tyre, 1966. (Folder 118: 39)
  - Soviet Information Bureau--"Falsificators ...,", 1948. (Folder 118: 40)
    Historical note
  - Soviet News Booklets
    - "East-West Trade," Spandaryan, V., 1954 (Folder 118: 41)
    - "Legal Rights ...," Sverdlov, G. M., 1945 (Folder 118: 42)
    - "We have Learned ...,", 1951 (Folder 118: 43)
  - Soviet Union--"Current Soviet Documents,", 1963. (Folder 118: 44)
  - Spanish Embassy--"Spain's War of Independence,", 1937. (Folder 118: 45)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc.--"Spanish Refugee Aid,", undated. (Folder 118: 46)
  - Spectator--"The Other Exodus," Childers, Erskine, 1961. (Box-folder 119: 1)
  - "Speeches and Statements of the Vice President ...,", 1959. (Folder 119: 2)
  - Spiritual Mobilization--"The Rightness of the Right to Work...," Greenfield, Edward W., 1958?. (Folder 119: 3)
  - SRT Publications--"Jungle Law or Human Reason?" Smith, Jessica, 1949. (Folder 119: 4)
  - Standard Publications
    - Tenney, Jack B.
      - "The Tenney Committee ...,", 1952. (Folder 119: 5)
      - "Zion's Fifth Column ...,", 1953. (Folder 119: 6)
    - Debs, Eugene V., "Unionism and Socialism,", 1904. (Folder 119: 7)
  - Stanley Foundation
    - "Ocean Management and World Order ...,", 1972. (Folder 119: 8)
    - "U.S. Nuclear Policy and Latin America,", 1976. (Folder 119: 9)
  - Starobin, Joseph, "The Life and Death ...,", 1938. (Folder 119: 10)
  - State Jewish Bureau of the Palestine Partition, Browder, Earl, and John Arnold, 1937. (Folder 119: 11)
  - State Publishing Company
    - "Secrets of the ...," Peters, J., 1947. (Folder 119: 12)
    - "Socialists' Plans ...,", 1961. (Folder 119: 13)
  - State's Rights Council of Georgia--Pittman, R. Carter
    - "Is Integration by Default ...,", 1960. (Folder 119: 14)
    - "The Supreme Court ...,", undated. (Folder 119: 15)
  - Sraver, William, "The Evils of Compulsory Unionism,", undated. (Folder 119: 16)
  - Steel Companies in the Wage Case--"The Double Standard ...," Austin, C. L., 1952. (Folder 119: 17)
  - Steel Workers of America--"Citizen Action for ...,", 1964. (Folder 119: 18)
  - Sterling Press--"The Palestine Mystery ...," Rogers, Arthur., 1948. (Folder 119: 19)
  - Stewart, Maco, "Communism,", undated. (Folder 119: 20)
  - Stickney, Charles, "Brain-Washing ...,", 1958?. (Folder 119: 21)
    Synthesis of a text book on psychopolitics
  - Wilson, J. Stitt
    - "The Kingdom of God and Socialism,", 1911. (Folder 119: 22)
    - "The Message of Socialism ...,", 1904. (Folder 119: 23)
  - Stoddard, Lothrop, "Gallery of Jewish ...,", undated. (Folder 119: 24)
  - Stoner Anti-Jewish Party--"The Gospel ...," Stoner, J. B., 1946. (Folder 119: 25)
  - Stoph, Willi, "Report on the Directives ...,", 1971. (Folder 119: 26)
  - Strickland Press
    - "Convict 9653 ...," Aldred, Guy A., 1942. (Folder 119: 27)
    - "Socialism and Parliament," Part II ..., Aldred, Guy A., 1942. (Folder 119: 28)
    - "The Struggle for Atomic Control," Fox, William T. R., 1947. (Folder 119: 29)
  - Students for a Democratic Society
    - "The Whole Thing was a Lie!" Duncan, Donald, 1965?. (Folder 119: 30)
    - "Huey Newton Talks to the Movement,", 1968. (Folder 119: 31)
  - Successful Farming--"Bolshevism ...," Schmidt, Louis Bernard, 1919. (Folder 119: 32)
  - Sullivan, George E., "Perfidious Planning,", 1947. (Folder 119: 33)
  - Supreme People's Assembly of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea--"The Letter to the Congress ...,", 1974 (Folder 119: 34)
  - Sword of the Lord Foundation--"Modernism ...," Weniger, G. Archer, 1961. (Folder 119: 35)
  - Synagogue Council of America--"Judaism and the ...," Wurzburger, Walter S., and Eugene B. Borowitz, undated. (Folder 119: 36)
  - Tanner, W. F., "One World Empire ...,", 1963. (Folder 119: 37)
  - Task Force for Economic Self-Education--"Goals for Americans," Ruthenburg, Louis, undated. (Folder 119: 38)
  - Taylor, Oral E., "Christianity ...,", 1963. (Folder 119: 39)
  - Teacher Publishing Company
    - "A Catholic Rebels," Fitzgerald, Gordon, 1962. (Folder 119: 40)
    - "A Handbook for Freedom Fighters," Ryker, Kenneth W., 1961. (Folder 119: 41)
  - Technocracy, Inc. (Box 120)
    - "America Must Show the Way,", 1938. (Folder 120: 1)
    - "A Continental Hydrology,", 1956. (Folder 120: 2)
    - "Continentalism: The Mandate for Survival,", 1947. (Folder 120: 3)
    - "The Energy Certificate,", 1937. (Folder 120: 4)
    - "Flying Wings for a Continental Offensive!", 1945. (Folder 120: 5)
    - "Man-Hours and Distribution," Hubbert, M. King, 1936. (Folder 120: 6)
    - "I Am the Price System ...,", 1938. (Folder 120: 7)
    - "Our Country: Right or Wrong,", 1946. (Folder 120: 8)
    - "Technocracy: Science vs. Chaos," Scott, Howard, 1933-1939. (Folder 120: 9-10)
    - "The Sellout of the Ages,", 1941. (Folder 120: 11)
    - "There'll Always Be an England,", 1946. (Folder 120: 12)
  - Tem Press--Pickett, Deets
    - An interview with Senator Estes Kefauver, 1951 (Folder 120: 13)
    - "Vice-Crime Web,", 1951 (Folder 120: 14)
  - Texas Power and Light Company--"These Truths We Must Hold ...,", undated. (Folder 120: 15)
  - Thames Publications--"The Mask Is Off ...," Woddis, Jack, 1954. (Folder 120: 16)
  - Theater Arts Committee and the Hollywood League for Democratic Action--"The Actors Present War," Hood, Richard, 1940. (Folder 120: 17)
  - "The One Thing that ...,", undated. (Folder 120: 18)
  - The Theosophist Office--"The Future Socialism," Besant, Annie, 1912. (Folder 120: 19)
  - Thomas A. Lane, "Vietnam: Observations ...,", 1967. (Folder 120: 20)
  - Thorin, Duane, "The Pugwash Movement ...,", 1965. (Folder 120: 21)
  - Through to Victory--"Win Now or Lose All," Neipp, Paul C., 1964. (Folder 120: 22)
  - Thunderbolt, Inc.
    - "Behind Communism," Britton, Frank L., undated. (Folder 120: 23)
    - "Jewish: A Ritual Murder," Leese, Arnold S., 1938. (Folder 120: 24)
    - "The African," Watson, Thomas E., undated. (Folder 120: 25)
  - The Tidings--"Communism Answers ...," Sheen, Fulton J., 1945. (Folder 120: 26)
  - Tilley, John, "Facts the Historians ...,", 1951. (Folder 120: 27)
  - Time, Inc.--"Willkie, We the People ...,", undated. (Folder 120: 28)
    Bookletc
  - Time for Truth Press--"The Commentators' Story," Close, Upton, undated. (Folder 120: 29)
    Broadcast scripts
  - Times Change Press--"Free Space ...," Allen, Pamela, 1970. (Folder 120: 30)
  - Toiler Publishing Association--"Stedman's Red Raid," Minor, Robert, 1921. (Folder 120: 31)
  - Tom Mooney Labor School--"History of the ...,", undated. (Folder 120: 32)
  - Tom Mooney Molders Defense Committee--"Pardon Tom Mooney ...," Griffin, Franklin A., 1929. (Folder 120: 33)
  - Tom Mooney Molders Defense Fund--"Tom Mooney's Message,", 1938. (Folder 120: 34)
  - Torchbearers of America, Inc.--"God's Light to Freedom,", 1961. (Folder 120: 35)
  - Trade Union Educational League
    - Foster, William Z.
      - "Organize and Unorganized,", undated. (Folder 120: 36)
      - "Strike Strategy,", 1926. (Folder 120: 37)
      - "Wrecking the Labor Bank,", 1927. (Folder 120: 38)
    - "Lenin ...," Losovsky, A., undated. (Box-folder 121: 1)
  - Trade Union Unity League--"Victorious Socialist ...," Foster, William Z., 1930. (Folder 121: 2)
  - Trader Publishing Company--"The Rulers of Russia," Fahey, Denis, 1938. (Folder 121: 3)
  - Tresca Memorial Committee--"Who Killed Carlo Tresca?", 1945. (Folder 121: 4)
  - Tribune Company--"Leftist Views Rule ...," Hughes, Frank, 1951. (Folder 121: 5)
  - "Trotsky-Stalin Conflict ...,", 1930. (Folder 121: 6)
  - Truth about Cuba Committee, Inc.
    - "Facts, Data ...,", 1956. (Folder 121: 7)
    - Manrara, Louis V.
      - "The Tricontinental Conference ...,", 1966?. (Folder 121: 8)
      - "Communist Methodology ...,", 1966. (Folder 121: 9)
  - Twentieth Century Crusaders--"Thus Speaks the Talmud,", 1936. (Folder 121: 10)
  - Twentieth Century Reformation Hour
    - McIntire, Carl
      - "Operation Whitewash ...,", undated. (Folder 121: 11)
        Reviews
      - "Massive Attack upon the Word of God,", 1964?. (Folder 121: 12)
      - "Operation 40,000,000,", 1961. (Folder 121: 13)
      - "Russian Orthodox Church,", 1963. (Folder 121: 14)
      - "Operation Abolition,", 1961. (Folder 121: 15)
      - "The Slaughter of the Innocents ...,", 1972. (Folder 121: 16)
      - "The Truth ...,", undated. (Folder 121: 17)
      - "UN Universal ...,", undated. (Folder 121: 18)
    - Matthews, J. B., "Communism in our Churches,", 1958. (Folder 121: 19)
  - Twin Circle Publishing Company--"Operation Suicide ..., Lyons, Eugene, 1967. (Folder 121: 20)
  - Tyndale House Publishers--"Anti-Christ's Temple," Clark, Doug, undated. (Folder 121: 21)
  - UAW Education Department--First annual report, 1957 (Folder 121: 22)
  - UAW-CIO
    - "How to Win for the Union,", 1943. (Folder 121: 23)
    - "The People are on the March," Wallace, Henry A., undated. (Folder 121: 24)
  - USSR Embassy, Information Department--"Fiftieth Anniversary ...,", 1967. (Folder 121: 25)
    Theses of the Central Committee of the Communist Party of the Soviet Union
  - "Underground Press Directory," fourth edition, 1970. (Folder 121: 26)
  - Underhill Publishing Company--"The Fascist Menace ...," Minton, Bruce, 1934. (Folder 121: 27)
  - Understandable Books--"You? In a Foreign Prison?" Reinhardt, Bryson, 1953. (Folder 121: 28)
  - Unidad Revolutionaries--"Cuban Revolutionary Unity ...,", 1963. (Folder 121: 29)
  - Union Deportiva de Cuba Libre--"Sports without Freedom ...,", 1962. (Folder 121: 30)
  - Union League of Philadelphia--"Saving the Union," Pepper, George Wharton, 1936. (Folder 121: 31)
  - Union Publishing Association--"The Role of the Labor Unions ...," Lozovsky, A. (Dridza), 1920. (Folder 121: 32)
  - United Automobile Workers of America--"The Pavement Trail ...,", 1946. (Folder 121: 33)
    Collection of poetry and prose
  - "United Auto, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America...," Reuther, Walter P., undated. (Folder 121: 34)
  - United Committee of South-Slavic Americans--"Liberation ...," Adamic, Louis, undated. (Folder 121: 35)
  - United Communist Party of America--"Theses and Statutes ...,", 1920. (Folder 121: 36)
  - United Community Church--"A Critique of the Center ...," McBirnie, W. S., undated. (Folder 121: 37)
  - "The World Council of Churches...," Murch, James DeForest, 1961. (Folder 121: 38)
  - United Front Press (Box 122)
    - "GI Revolts ...," Boyle, Richard, 1972. (Folder 122: 1)
    - "The Energy Crisis ...," Pugh, Dave, and Mitch Zimmerman, 1974. (Folder 122: 2)
  - United Labor and People's Committee for May Day--"May Day 1951," Fast, Howard, circa 1951. (Folder 122: 3)
  - United Nations Publications
    - "Basic Facts about the United Nations,", 1953. (Folder 122: 4)
    - "Charter of the United Nations ...,", undated. (Folder 122: 5-6)
    - "Decisions and Prospects for 1953," (Folder 122: 7)
    - "How the United Nations Began,", 1951. (Folder 122: 8)
    - "United Nations: The Road to Disaster,", undated. (Folder 122: 9)
    - "Human Rights in the United Nations,", 1952. (Folder 122: 10)
    - "Our Rights as Human Beings,", 1949. (Folder 122: 11)
    - "Sharing Skills ...,", 1953. (Folder 122: 12)
    - "Visitors' Guide to the United Nations,", 1953. (Folder 122: 13)
    - "What the United Nations Is Doing ...,", 1952. (Folder 122: 14)
    - "World Social Situation Today ...,", 1952. (Folder 122: 15)
    - "Your United Nations,", 1953. (Folder 122: 16)
      Official souvenir guide book
  - UN Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)
    - "The Education and Training ...,", 1949. (Folder 122: 17)
    - "The Influence of Home ...,", 1949. (Folder 122: 18)
    - "Race and Psychology," Klineberg, Otto, 1951. (Folder 122: 19)
    - "The Roots of Prejudice," Rose, Arnold M., 1951. (Folder 122: 20)
    - "In the Classroom ...,", 1949. (Folder 122: 21)
    - "History Text Books ...," Lauwerys, J. A., undated. (Folder 122: 22)
    - "A Selected Bibliography ...,", undated. (Folder 122: 23)
      Bibliography
    - "Some Suggestions on Teaching ...,", 1952. (Folder 122: 24)
    - "The United Nations and World Citizenship ...,", 1949. (Folder 122: 25)
    - "The Universal Declaration ...,", 1953. (Folder 122: 26)
    - "What Is Race?", 1952. (Folder 122: 27)
  - "University Bookman," edited by Kirk, Russell, 1989. (Folder 122: 28)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce--"Is Your Plant a Target?", 1951. (Folder 122: 29)
  - U.S. Government Printing Office--Knowland, William F., 1952. (Folder 122: 30)
  - U.S. Army Command and General Staff College--"Nature of Communism,", undated. (Folder 122: 31)
  - U.S. Department of Interior--"Saline Water Conversion ...,", undated. (Folder 122: 32)
  - U.S. Government Printing Office
    - "Misquotations of the Constitution ...," Hayden, Carl, 1954. (Folder 122: 33)
    - "Communist Persecution ...,", 1959. (Folder 122: 34)
    - "America's Retreat from Victory ...," McCarthy, Joseph, 1951. (Folder 122: 35)
  - U.S. Department of State--"Freedom from War: The United States Program for General and Complete Disarmament in a Peaceful World,", 1961. (Folder 122: 36)
  - U.S. Government Printing Office (Box 123)
    - Malone, George W.
      - "A Conspiracy ... Investors," "The Domestic Economy ..." and "Fair and Reasonable ...," Malone, George W., 1955. (Folder 123: 1)
      - "Minority Report ...," Malone, George W., 1955. (Folder 123: 2)
        Speech and extract from Senate report
    - "Democratic Party ...," Robinson, Joseph T., 1936. (Folder 123: 3)
    - "The Bricker ...," Smith, Wint, 1954. (Folder 123: 4)
    - "Committee on Un-American Activities ...,", 1948. (Folder 123: 5)
      Interim report
    - "Actions to Frustrate ...," Thurmond, Strom, 1961. (Folder 123: 6)
    - "Excerpts from Speeches by Senator Strom Thurmond ...,", 1961. (Folder 123: 7)
    - "Senator Thurmond and Tower ...,", 1961. (Folder 123: 8)
    - "The United Nations and the Peace," Wheeler, Burton K., 1945. (Folder 123: 9)
    - "Why Vietnam ...," Johnson, Lyndon, 1965. (Folder 123: 10)
      Extracts from letters
    - "How our Laws ...," Zinn, Charles J., 1961. (Folder 123: 11)
  - U.S. Marine Corps--"How to Respect and Display our Flag,", undated. (Folder 123: 12)
  - U.S. Department of State--"Freedom from War ...,", 1961. (Folder 123: 13)
  - U.S. National Student Association--"Human Relations ...," Medalie, Richard J., 1950. (Folder 123: 14)
  - University of Arizona--"The Emergence of the Secular ...," Williams, Edward J., 1971. (Folder 123: 15)
  - University of California, Berkeley--"Communism in Asia ...," Scalapino, Robert A., 1965. (Folder 123: 16)
  - University of Chicago Press--"Let's Join ...," Barr, Stringfellow, 1950. (Folder 123: 17)
  - University of Illinois--"The University and the War,", 1942. (Folder 123: 18)
  - University of Virginia Press--"Magna Carta ...," Howard, A. E. Dick, 1964. (Folder 123: 19)
  - "Unteilbares Deutschland—Berlin ...,", 1961. (Folder 123: 20)
  - Upton Sinclair--"The Parlor ...,", 1923. (Folder 123: 21)
  - Urban Renewal Department--City of Phoenix, "City of Phoenix ...,", 1959. (Folder 123: 22)
  - Verlag Zeit im Bild
    - "The Lessons ...,", 1970. (Folder 123: 23)
    - "Hitler's Chief Agitator ...," Norden, Albert, 1966. (Folder 123: 24)
    - "The Role of the Socialist State ...," Ulbricht, Walter, 1968. (Folder 123: 25)
    - "Peace ...," Davis, Angela, undated. (Folder 123: 26)
    - "Protocol of the Press Conference ...," Ulbricht, Walter, 1970. (Folder 123: 27)
    - "Statement of the Council of Ministers ...,", 1970. (Folder 123: 28)
  - Vietnam, undated. (Folder 123: 29)
    Anti-war pamphlet for African Americans
  - Vietnam Committee of the Afro-Asian Solidarity of the German Democratic Republic--"The West German ...,", 1966. (Folder 123: 30)
  - Vietnamese Studies--"North Vietnamese ...,", 1967. (Folder 123: 31)
  - Vietnam Veterans against War--"Demonstrate July 4th ...,", undated. (Folder 123: 32)
  - Vietnam Council on Foreign Relations--"Vietnam: ...," Honey, P. J., 1971. (Folder 123: 33)
  - Viewpoint, 1944. (Folder 123: 34)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade--"Western Front Now!" Wolff, Milton, 1941. (Folder 123: 35)
  - Victor Publishing Company--"Must Barry Goldwater ...?", 1964. (Folder 123: 36)
  - Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government
    - "Civil Rights and Legal Wrongs,", 1963. (Folder 123: 37)
      Critical commentary
    - "The Civil Rights Cases," Justice Bradley, 1883. (Folder 123: 38)
    - "The Constitutionality ...," Button, Robert Y., undated. (Folder 123: 39)
      Response to the attorney general of the United States
    - "Every Man Did ...,", 1967. (Folder 123: 40)
    - "The Bill of Rights ...," Harlan, John M., 1964. (Folder 123: 41)
    - "Voting Rights and Legal Wrongs,", undated. (Folder 123: 42)
    - "Sockdolager!" Crockett, David, 1961. (Folder 123: 43)
    - "Virginia's Answers ...,", 1963. (Folder 123: 44)
  - Vanzetti, Bartolomew--"Background of the Plymouth Trial,", undated. (Folder 123: 45)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars--"Americanism," Wilson, Woodrow, Theodore Roosevelt, and Franklin K. Lane, 1915-1919. (Folder 123: 46)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade--"Spain in Chains," Sanchez-Mazas, Miguel, undated. (Folder 123: 47)
  - Vigilant Women for the Bricker Amendment--"The American Plan for UN ...,", 1955. (Box-folder 124: 1)
  - Vincent Press
    - "The Teenage Mind and ...," Husted, Ralph W., undated. (Folder 124: 2)
      Comments on the report of the National Task Force on Economic Education
    - "The Socialistic Sixteenth ...," Clark, Fred G., undated. (Folder 124: 3)
  - Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government
    - "A Country without a Man ...,", 1958. (Folder 124: 4)
    - "Federal Subsidies ...,", 1963. (Folder 124: 5)
    - "A Question of Intent ...," Mays, David J., 1959. (Folder 124: 6)
    - "Nor Cruel and ...," Kilpatrick, James J., 1965. (Folder 124: 7)